FWD Podcast bluntly free [music]
steps to discuss protection with
FWD insurance.  Just be blunt.
Hi Fion people, welcome back to the FWD
podcast with me Madam
Sally Celebrate Living.  This episode is
very special because we will enter the
Chinese New Year which will be a
special moment for all passionate people.   It's
not just about celebration, but it's
also about hope, reflection,
and new beginnings.  As we enter a
new year.  Hey, at the start of
last year, in January,
I didn't feel like there was a
shifting energy like that, passionate
people.  E, maybe there are some who are
more enthusiastic, there are also some who are a bit
nervous.  Hopefully the deans will
remain excited because they want to celebrate
living in the new year.  In this episode,
Madam Sally is not alone because she is
present with a
very special speaker, namely,
reader Patse Pat Bazi.  Maybe
we'll ask Brother Bijo directly
what he reads later to provide
various information that Pion People can
use to support Celebrate Living in
this new year.  Just call me straight away, okay?
Hello, Brother Bijo.  O.  Hi Madam
Si.  Hi Passionate People.  Thank you so
much for having me in the session.
Let me introduce myself, I'm Bijo.  I am a
PS.
How are you, Bijo?  How are you?
Ah, eh thankfully.  Thank goodness.  Madam
Selli, how are you?  Are you healthy, G?
Healthy, G everyone is really excited
because this year is the
same year as Seo and I.
Oh I see.  Is it the year of the horse?
Horse.  And I'm also a Fire Element.
So, that's why I've felt really enthusiastic since the beginning of the year,
like I'm on
fire.  Okay.
When you say ee bazi, do
you pronounce it bazi or is there another language?
Oh yes.  Okay.  If for ee, the way
to say it is PS Pse, right?  PSE passionate
people.  So we will explore again
about PATSE in relation to Chinese
New Year.  Well, I just want to ask
Brother Bijo directly.   Of course you
can.  Okay, based on the
Chinese Metaphysics Calendar,
the change of the year of the horse has
officially happened now, right? On the
date ee today or yesterday, I've
forgotten.
Okay.  So, as we know,
we always celebrate it,
whether it's at the end of January or mid-
February or maybe right around the
turn of the year.  But
in the Chinese Metaphysics Calendar,
the change of year usually occurs at the beginning of
spring, between February 3 or 4
.  So even though we will be
celebrating Chinese New Year on February 17th
, on the 4th we
already celebrated the New Year.  That's right.  So
now we are in Fireh.
Passionate people.  yes.  Well, but
actually, this reading, maybe
we've discussed it before, but I
want to refresh myself.  Who
knows, maybe there are people who are not yet
aware of this passion when reading what it
actually is.  What is ple reading,
Sis?  E Bijo.
Hehe.  Okay.  So, maybe I'll
give you an idea first.  So PSE
is one of the derivatives of Chinese
Metaphysics, Passionate People.  So
Chinese Metaphysics is an
umbrella.  There are many derivatives.
Maybe people who are passionate about
Madam S have heard that one of
her descendants is Feng.
we are in the same one but have
different functions more or less like
that.  Well, so maybe there are many
passionate people or Madam S or
all of your friends who see
this PS as a tool or instrument for
reading life lines or destiny.
Although actually it's not 100%
wrong, because
we say that every human being has their own
lessons, they have their own chapters in
life.
Sometimes passionate people, ee, maybe
there is a perception that pats sio fengu is
like a fortune-telling, actually, is it a
kabijo fortune-telling like
that.  [laughs]
Hey, how do you read it?
So actually, it's like this, it's like
maybe many people see PS
as a tool or instrument
for reading destiny or
life lines.  It's just that I believe, I
believe that everyone has their own
power and also control to create the life
that they want.  So I believe that
every human being can choose like that.
So why do I always say that
think of it as our Google Maps, it
helps us navigate to see
our good and bad talents.
Because again, we can
maximize the good potential and also
minimize the bad.
In other words, it helps us to be
strategic, right?  Oh, well, let's get
straight to it, maybe you're
really curious to see PS's perspective for the
year of the fire horse.
If we look at the characters themselves, eh, fire
and horse, like, eh, one
horse moves fast, right? The other
fire explodes and goes up and
spreads really fast, right?  Are we
entering a year where everything will
change rapidly or
what are the characteristics of
this year and how
will its energy affect our lives
for the next year?
Okay.  Well, so this is what it's like,
passionate people, in my personal opinion,
really describe the
firework year because it's so fiery.  And
indeed, in general, this year has been
full of passion, full of
enthusiasm, and enthusiasm.  But
this fire is indeed moving very fast, isn't it?
And in the Pse method, the horse falls
into a category called peach blasem.
Oh.
So, we can say that peach blasem is
closely related to things
related to charisma,
communication skills, and connections.  So
this is indeed the year where we are invited
to see our self-worth.
confident, sociable, connected.  However,
this year there is no water element
or element of ya, where water
represents adaptability,
flexibility, and also wisdom.
So, this year we are
invited to be brave enough to show up, know
our worth, be confident, socialize,
connect, but also remain wise.
Including emotional and
financial management.  Am I a bit
worried?  There's no water
because our fire [laughs] was taught
that there are primas before this,
what should there be if the fire
suddenly catches fire, then
eh, there's no fire, eh, there's no water, then there's no one to
put it out.  Ee actually
ee
I was also looking for a bit yesterday
, ee bro Bijo.  Hey, this year we
entered period one, and last year
it was period n, which means
ending and we entered a new era
, a new beginning.  Is it
right for us, Sis, to
start something new this year?
Okay, so actually,
from Chinese Metaphysics, since last year
we have entered period 9, and
this period will continue
until 2044. So it's a long
period and period 9 is also defined
by the fire elements.  So indeed, we are
already in the N period and it is
also the year of the fire horse.  So yes, for some people, you
might see this year of the fire horse
as a long summer, in quotation marks
.  Okay.  Okay.  Well, as a
new year, Sis, ee for passionate people,
maybe there are many things that have been done, ee
, what are your targets for entering the
new year.  Ee, between wanting to have a new business
or maybe many people want
to try new things like that.  Is
this the right year to try
new things?
Okay, actually it's like this.  Um, this depends, it
depends.  Because if we
talk about new things, actually the
personal impact on our friends is of
course different.  But maybe
I'll give you more hints
, what kind of shows like
this can maximize the good potential
in the year of the fire horse.  Okay, back again,
maybe a little bit of a hint too because
this year in quotation marks will be
quite hot, you know.  Um, what needs to
be noted earlier is the burnout aspect,
so we are invited to be wiser in
managing our emotions, mental health
and so on.  And secondly, uh, it
could also happen, we call it
competition in the global market
or business or maybe in areas where
influential people might be involved,
because this is a hot year, in
quotation marks.  So, how do we do this
or how can we maximize
the good potentials?  The first one
comes back to management, yes,
email management because it must be
parallel, right, people.  And
maybe there are a few shows that I
want to give you some tips on
how you can maximize them
if you want to try something new this year.
Okay, so for the first two shows, the ones
who will probably get blessings from
the partnership business are tigers and
dogs.
Again, it was from a business perspective, right, Sis?
earlier there were tigers and also dogs.
Dog.  Well, from another aspect, okay,
so maybe I'll explain a little bit first
about the tiger and the dog.  So
we call these tigers, dogs and horses
natural allies or harmony.
So we can say that these are two
shows that can benefit from
collaboration or business partnership
because they are good friends, you could say
.  Well, then next there will be a
third show, maybe
this is a good year to try something
new.  E I can say maybe come back
year yeah.  That's a goat.
Why is it that goats come back
this year?
That's right.  Because eh, maybe the last 2 years, there were a
lot of lessons and
so on, and this year was a
pretty bright year for the
goat friends.  So this is your
year to maximize the good potentials
.  Well, maybe there are two shows
that are interesting in my opinion.  So, these two shows
are friends whose charisma
will increase even more this year.
Oh, because the peach blasem is not?
That's right.  Because these two shows are
peach blossom friends, namely
rabbits and chickens, right?  So for
friends who have show rabbits
or chickens, this is also your year
to shine.  Okay.  So, I want to give you
some tips too.  For example, if your
friends in your ee group, in your team,
for example the marketing team, you want to
try looking for people to be on the front line,
for example live on social media, and then in
your team there are friends who show
rabbits or chickens, try
inviting them to perform.  Maybe you can
gather more messages like that.
Well, that means it's time for passionate people who
have peaches, blasems, rabbits, and chickens to come
forward.
That's it.  For example, if you are friends of
rabbits and chickens, there are passionate people
here who have rabbits and chickens, if
you want to try personal branding too,
why not?  Because it could be
one of the businesses that will
progress this year.
Very interesting.  This means that Pzer reading
not only looks at characteristics, but
can also see industry trends
.  If this is the year of the fire horse,
what do you think the trends will be for the next year,
from an industrial perspective
?
Okay.  So maybe for example for
TEK it will continue, ee, because
we are also in a period.
That's right.  Technology will keep going, right?
Earlier, perhaps
industries related
to social media and technology
will definitely continue to keep going.
personal branding.
I personal branding.  That's right.  Will go up
potentially will go up.  Then,
industries that also provide
perhaps e or increase self-
expression, creativity, yes, that will also
increase significantly.  The entertainment industry
can also increase, including the beauty
industry, because it is also included
in the fire category, and also e-food
or food also has the potential to increase
like that.  Okay.  Hey, if we talk about
fire and horse, it's all about what,
seeing that it's fast, ee, in a hurry,
maybe sometimes you reflect on
yourself as a horse, right?  [laughs] Hey,
what do you think, Sis?  Are there any tips and tricks
so that we
can be prepared so that we don't get
burned by the existing fire?
this speed.  That's right.
Truly.  So, of course, the first thing we need is
mindfulness, staying
grounded.  For
example, if we have moments that make us
worry or anxious, we definitely need
breathing exercises or maybe physical
exercises.  So mental and
physical health are very, very necessary, and of
course, good health protection is also needed
.  Because, uh, I think, if
there are some
passionate people who have been with
me, and if there are phases,
uh, there might be potential ups and
downs and so on, I like to
suggest investing in the
right health insurance for
protection, so that I can maximize
good potential and minimize bad talents
.  Yes, that's absolutely true.  Honestly,
as someone in the insurance industry, I
see that insurance can be
a strategy for us
to prepare ourselves for various risks that are
not currently visible.
So, ee living a life of celebrating
living can be more peaceful like that.  So,
what kind of mindset should we have, Sis?  ee so that ee
we can
use this fire horse energy
well and of course it is not inferior to
this burning fire so that we do
n't burn out.  We have
to be like, ee, besides resting
or breathing works, is there any
other preparation from
this PATse that you can tell us about?  Okay,
actually, there might be a lot of them
if you ask us what
kind of mindset we have or what
we can do.  Actually, there are lots
of things, but in my opinion, the most
practical thing is that we want to
balance ourselves first.  We also want to
try new things at the same time.  Because
remember, fire is still a moving element, right?
So, it comes back to the
balancing act, how do we
dare to keep going, be confident, dare to
appear, connect, put ourselves out
there, that's
right.  But also at the same time
be mindful and wise.  That's it, that's
it.  So, for example, if we talk about practical
things,
we can do breathing exercises, grounding, physical
exercises, and also
health protection.  That's right.  So ee
maybe we can do it in parallel like
that.  And it also comes back to the topic of
financial management, because
this year is a year that might
make some passionate people more
impulsive than in
previous years.   That's
right, don't let your money get
burned by the fire horse, okay?
Yes  We have to maximize the
good potential and minimize the bad ones
.
OK, maybe there are a lot of passionate people
who want to
know more about the reading part, right?  I think I
want to read this.  Okay.
Okay.   The
chart is fine. You've probably already
learned to read charts.
Okay, okay.  Let's start from there, okay?
Hey.
Okay.  Eh, by the way this is the
Fire Horse chart.  This is this year's chart.  But
I might as well just explain
how to read
the
fourth day of our show.  We have four
shows by the way, Passionate People.  So
maybe after this we can also give
some hints for other shows.   Just now there were
dogs,
tigers, rabbits, and chickens, right?
Later we will try to provide other clues
too.
Horse itself, Sis.
Yes, do you have your own horse yet?  After this
we read.
Okay, [laughs] go ahead.  Okay.  Well, so e
Passionate People maybe eh I'm sure e
already have many friends who know
how to read the P chart.  Eh, for
today, maybe I will share more,
eh, what is a P chart,
what does it look like?  Okay, the
important thing is that passionate people already
know their birth date and time
first.  Okay.  Well, because in the PSE method
we can have up to four shows,
not just one show, Madam S.
Oh, because usually we read
it like a zodiac, you know, we only
know one.  There are four of them.
That's right.  That's right.  Yes.  So what we often
hear is show.  Okay.  Like here
this year it's a fire horse, right?
Okay.  Well, so passionate people
can enter any kind of
website p everywhere.  Yes, ee, what I mean is that
nowadays there are so many search engines,
so you can just choose
one of the websites, passionate people,
just enter your personal data, name, date of
birth, time of birth, then click submit or
plot chart, usually it's written like
that.  Okay.  Well, then it will look
more or less like this, the box.
So, there will be four pillars.  Well,
there is a day pillar,
there is a month pillar, a year pillar, and also an
hour pillar.  Okay.  Well, these four pillars
also represent the sectors of
human life.  Well, what we
hear most often is this year's show.
Later, there will be writing on this side, the
writing will be there, last year,
here, what kind of shows.  Like
this year, which is the year of the fire horse.  Well,
then passionate people.  If passionate
people want to see, there is one
important aspect in the PCE method, namely the
day master or the main element where the day
master is determined by our date of birth
.
That's right.  So, for example, if
passionate people want to check
what their day master is, passionate people
just have to look and there will be writing on
these four pillars, there is writing on day,
usually it is located here, there is
writing on day.  Well, right below that
are the passionate people.
There are 10 day masters, namely wood, yin
wood, yang fire, yin fire, yang earth,
yin earth, yang metal, yin metal, yang
water, and yin water.  There are 10 of them, right?
So, eh, day master passionate people is
one of the 10 elements.
OK, that day is the main element
or core of who we are.  Well, then
passionate people can see in the area
below the day master, which is
our shoari or day animal sign area.  Well, so eh, for
example, if we look here, the day
master is Hin Earth, for
example, and the day master is Rooster
.  So for the sio hari or day
pillar of that person in the PAsa method
is ground chicken.  So that's how to
check dayillar.  Okay.  If earlier there
was fire, wood, e wood, earth, water,
and metal, each of them has its own characteristics,
right?
If it's fire now, usually
earth or water and wood are
different too,
what are their characteristics, Sis?
Okay, we might have a rough idea.
Rough sketch, yes.  Okay, maybe we
'll start from fire first,
guys.  Fire, my friends, is what
I can say lights up the room, you know
.  Just like the fire.
They enlighten the room.  They
become an encouragement.  They are
passionate friends again, passionate people like that
.  That's fire.  Well, then
there is the earth element.  After fire
we have earth.  These earth friends are
friends who I can say are idealistic
and have principles, right?  They have
something that cannot be disturbed
.  And the friends that I can
say are the most caring are those on the
right and left.  Well, next there is the
metal element.  This metal is for friends who
have systematic thinking, have
structure, have an eye for details and
don't like it when their plans fail.  That's
metal, right?
Yes.  Then there is water.  Well,
these water friends are adaptable,
spontaneous and flowing friends, more like going
with the flow.
Well, the last one is wood.  This wood,
friends, I can say is a bit
stiff.  [laughs] But
friends who like to explore and want to
find something new,
because if we look at wood
as an element, it is the only element
that can grow by itself,
keep growing, you know.  That's what
wooden friends are
like.
Pull it yeah.  So [laughs] each of them
has its own differences and there are
definitely strengths and weaknesses.
Yes, that's for sure.  Well, so that was the
day pillar.  Well, then if Passionate
People see there are three other shows like that.
Well, in this area is the moon show.  Okay, for
example, if we look here, the
month is tiger.  Then at
this year's show, yes, the fire horse.  Then on the clock
there is also another tiger.  So, if
passionate people enter the
data, it will definitely be different
from this chart.  Here, just an example
.  So later, Passionate People will be able to
know what the four Passionate People shows are
and they can be different or
all the same.  Again, everyone is
different.
Okay, now we want to get into the
most exciting part, namely mini reading
with Kijo.  E here Kijo will
recite the dayas earlier, that's it.
I've already mentioned that the origin of one passionate
person's data.  Hey, so what do you think, Sis?
What are the pillars of these passionate people?
Okay, maybe a little outline
this year, so it can give you an
idea.
Oh, for all shows, yeah.
Oh, that's right.  But later we will go to passionate
people whose data I already have,
then we will go to all shows.
Okay.
Okay.  So, earlier I got some
data on passionate people.  It turns out that when
I checked, the master was the metal one.
Well, so where is it for passionate
people who have each metal that
I saw earlier, eh, potential this year,
maybe their career will improve too, right?
Because this year, the passionate
people whose chart I just read
have that kind of star power.  Where is
this and if I may ask, what is the chart,
Sis?  The results of the
eight pillars
.
Oh okay.  For example, maybe I'll just go to the
pillar that day.  for the pillar of
the day is the metal tiger.  Just now when I
checked, that's what it was.  So the metal tiger is
for the day master area or the
heavenly area, it must be metal or
large metal.  So, for
this year, there will probably be
career advancement, maybe there
will be
new responsibilities, and learning to make
decisions too.  And for
this year, the passionate people
I read about earlier can also learn many
new things for this year.  And earlier
I had a peek, yes, the
lunar pillar has the goat where
this goat this year is quite what
I said earlier is lit, yes, like a come back
year and there is also potential for
goat friends, maybe it can
also be noted for passionate people
who have goats, there will be help from
male figures in your life and
this can be personal or professional
depending on where the goat is, passionate
people are.  If earlier,
what I read was that the
goat show was in the moon area, where the
moon area can be related to
professional life.
Oh, that's interesting.  Uh, congratulations to the
passionate people who
read it earlier.
[laughs] So this year I'm ready
to go forward with a message that matches my
horse's sio.
Okay, next time there's still something else, or would you
like to just go straight to it so that other people can
get some too?  Correct.  Well, since
we've already given you some hints
, how do you read the four shows?
So, earlier, passion with people was okay,
maybe, while I was watching the
show, what were the things like that?  So, don't
just show the year that passionate
people check, but everything so that we
can maximize or navigate the year of the
fire horse even better.  Okay,
maybe we've already discussed
tigers, then dogs, rabbits, chickens,
goats too.  Well, maybe it's the horse
itself.  Okay.  It's the year of the horse,
are horses lucky too?  Fion.
Okay.  So for my horse friends,
this is actually a year that can make
you successful.  However,
emotional management is
also key because for Horse friends
this year there are financial blessings,
there is the potential for promotion, being seen
as important people in your
community, in your collective, in your
company, perhaps.  potential
to be the person who is needed.  And
friends, when we are in a position
that is perhaps high, yes, we are in office,
we get a new title,
of course there are new responsibilities.
And are you ready to make decisions this
year for your horse friends here?
Yes, yes, yes.  [laughs]
I'm sure because watching horses is
watching something passionate, and eh,
success matters, which is really a great deal to
horses actually.  So, my
friends are indeed ambitious.  OK,
so this is actually able to be your year.
But just manage your emotions.
And remember, focus on your lane.
Just focus on your goals,
your priorities.  No need to look right and left like
that.  That's for horses this year.
Next, Sis, what else is there?
Okay, next is the outline for my
fellow rats, this year is
pretty unexpected for you guys.
So, the best investment is an
investment in health, both mental and
physical.  For example, with
yoga classes, meditation
or
outdoor activities, that's the most important thing.
Why?  Because unexpected things can be
unexpected blessings, but they can also be
unexpected shifts in plans.
Where, for example, if plans
change, that's something beyond
our control, right?  That's why maybe
sometimes it can make us emotional
and so on.  So, it's very important for
rat friends to stay at your own
pace, okay?  Just follow your pace, don't
look left or right, and stay mindful and
grounded.  Okay, earlier the mouse horse was already a
buffalo, it seems like it hasn't been mentioned yet, but
I can say that in terms of career, it will be
really good.  potential maybe
promotion seen by people will be more likely to
be able to come back again maybe the same yes
new responsibilities but with
different stars.  Okay.  Hey, career-wise,
this year for the Ox is really good, but you do
need to be wiser in
any kind of relationship.  So, because
you are being looked at like that, you need to be
wiser in your communication or
in your relationships with other people,
in relationships.  That's
for the buffalo friends.  Well, maybe
there is something similar to a buffalo
.  That career position is
really good, that dragon is really on the rise.   There were
n't any dragons yet.  Yes
This dragon, I can say, is also in a
good position in terms of career, in terms of
professional life.  E will be the one to
look at too.  But this is very
interesting for Dragon friends,
where
the theme for that year is work-life balance
, where work is important, productivity is important,
but also mindfulness.
So even though you are at the top, you still
have to maintain
mindfulness.  That's right, mindfulness.  After the
dragon, maybe we have a snake.
Snake huh.
Snake, I can say what year this is
?  Eh, it's actually a leisurely walk or leisure
time.  Because
there are interesting stars
for snake friends to
enjoy life more.  More
actually, eh, more mindful, but
there's also a bit of a leure star in it.
We can say that the stars are probably
having fun, enjoying life too
.  Celebrate,
that's right, celebrate living.  Well, I
always say that even when there are
good stars for enjoying life, we
still have to protect ourselves so we
can maximize our good potential, you know
.  Because it would be useless if, for example,
there was a traveling star, going on a trip.
If for example we do
that, we won't be able to enjoy it.
Well, after we have snakes, maybe
we haven't read about monkeys, there are
pigs.  Hehe.  Monkey and pig.
This is really interesting.
But I might separate it for the
monkeys.  This is actually your year, if you
want, maybe study or learn new
things.  Okay, that's the first one.  Maybe
this is your year to upgrade your skills
as in professional or
academic education.  This is also your year.
Potential for example resigning or moving.  Hehe.
That's right.  Pivot career.  That's right.  Or
shifting, yes.  That could be the case too.  So
there is a change, a shift
or we could say an increase in
self-worth, that's also possible.  That's for the
monkey friends, okay?  Well, Leslie
might be a pig.  Well, for this pig,
actually the reason I said it was
similar is because the theme is also
upgrading your values.  So if
your pig friends are, uh,
maybe a business owner, this is
actually your year or a good time
to upgrade perhaps your assets or
maybe dare to show yourself in the
global market.  Maybe you want to try a
bazaar in a new place that you have
never tried before.  Why not be
right like that for pig friends like that.
OK, thank you so much Sis Bijo.  12 is
complete, all of it is read, the weakness
of the tr.  But to get the most out
of this year of the fire horse, do you
have any other tips?
That's right.  So actually, one thing for
sure, passionate people, every year there
are good and bad stars
.  So, I think we can do more to
maximize our potential
using the methods mentioned above.  The more
mindful we are, the more confident we are.
dare to connect this year and also be
wise.  This year is the year that invites
us to learn to manage ourselves
, manage our emotions, manage our
finances and also our health.   That's
why we have to
maximize it.  I like to say this,
if you're not healthy, you can't make money
, you can't maximize your income
.  So, health protection
is also very important, especially
how we choose the
right health insurance.  Okay, and this is where
insurance plays a role,
right, Brother Bijo.  Hey, FWD Insurance
also has products for you to
protect yourself and your family,
Passionate People.  EE is not only
to support yourself and your family, but
can also support you to celebrate living,
starting from life insurance, health insurance,
personal accident insurance, even
insurance linked to
EE investments or unit links.  So,
this year is not for us to stop,
but we have to maximize our
celebration of life.  Passionate
people.  Do you agree, Brother Bijo?
Agree.
Well, for passionate people who don't
have insurance yet, FD Insurance
has products that can be purchased
via WhatsApp, directly from
WhatsApp.  E and also on the
website fw.co.id.
Not only that, we're having a
really special Chinese New Year promotion,
offering premium discounts of up to 27% on
digital insurance products, which can be
purchased directly through the website using the
promo code CNY26
.  Once again the promo code is CNY26.
For further information, Passion People
can directly check the website
fwinsurancefwd.co.
co.id we have already learned about
the reading part, ee, it has been explained earlier what the
day master is like.  Eh, I've
read the reading, eh, the master day
master of Passionate People 12
has also been mentioned.
E, before we close this podcast
, Brother Bijo, do you have any important message
for passionate
people so they can continue to celebrate living
in the year of Firehorses?
Okay, Wanting for sure must remain
confident and also wise
this year, okay?  Remember, emotional and
financial management is important.  Likewise with
choosing the right health insurance.
Okay, thank you KBO for reading.
Earlier we learned about what PSE
reading is like.  Hey, thank you
for reading Passionate People
, what was your day like?  Ee, basically
passionate people, hopefully you can
prepare your new year
better and maximize it to
celebrate your life, Sis.  Thank you
so much passionate people who have
listened from beginning to end.  Don't
forget to follow FWD Insurance's Instagram account
at @fwd_id
because we have a special prize for two
winners, namely a summary
reading from Kak Bijo directly.
Yes.  So later there will be two
lucky passionate people who will
get the P yearly horse summary.  So
later, the summary will be
sent directly to Passionate People's email.
So all the data is
confidential too.  Oh, what are the conditions?
Of course, Madam Seli will
inform you later.  And if my requirement is that
Passionate People have a
birth date and time, that's all
.  Okay, so stay tuned to
Passionate People on FW_id
on Instagram.  Later,
we will put the questions there and
of course we will contact you directly
there.  So it will not be connected
from other lines.
That's right.
Okay, then stay tuned for the
quiz details and of course keep an eye on
FWD Insurance Indonesia's YouTube channel
for the next episode of the FWD Podcast
with Madam Sally and there will
also be other passionate people
who are experts present to discuss
things that are relevant to passionate
people to celebrate living.  PT FWD
Insurance Indonesia.  F Insurance is registered
and supervised by the Financial Services Authority
or OJK.  See you in the
next episode.  Celebrate
people.